Nothing's there.
They're both empty.
Other than this piece of paper…
The scent has transferred
outside the pocket…
Could it be…
It's just a blank piece of paper.
What?!
BLAM
J-Josuke!
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:42 PM
SWIP
You really stepped in it!
Goodness, you should really
be more careful.
I warned you about
the fire damage up here, didn't I?
I honestly don't see
what all the fuss is about.
You have a very respectable back…
I-It's over… I'm through…
It doesn't make any sense…
I have this horrible feeling I'm
gonna die if someone sees my back!
H-Hey…
It's too late, I'm as good as dead!
Just calm yourself down.
I'm sorry.
My curiosity got
the best of me and…
What in the?!
He was attacked by a Stand!
The Stand attached itself
to his back?!
If it did, Heaven's Door
wouldn't be able to…
Of course, his notes
wouldn't reveal that.
He was already overcome
by the time he go there.
This architect is the victim.
The Stand overwhelmed him
to get to me.
Piggyback, please.
It's here! It's the enemy Stand!
Let's play piggyback, okay?
Piggyback, please.
Piggyback… piggyback, please?
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
JULY 15TH (THURS) 1:39 PM
Here's a list of
missing persons cases in Morioh,
including runaways.
EPISODE 33
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 3
The data reflects the period
after Kira's disappearance,
hence the small number.
So some could very well
be Kira's victims.
We don't know for sure,
that is a possibility.
At this point,
we have to follow his every move.
Even the most seemingly
insignificant of activities
can have a far-reaching effect.
M PREFECTURE S CITY,
MISSING PERSONS
Time and time again.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:55 PM
Piggyback, please?
Piggyback.
Heaven's Door!
Piggyback, please?
Piggyback.
What?! I don't believe it…
It's attached itself to my back?
Did it latch onto me because
I looked at the architect's back?
Blast it!
Ignite the pictures…
Please, ignite the pictures.
The pictures?
Ignite them, please?
Get rid of the pictures…
What are you talking about?
These are the pictures I took…
Could one of them be…
Could one of them lead us
to Yoshikage Kira…
You're trying to get rid of it…
Just ignite them all, please?
You get rid of them, yes?
Shut up, you parasite!
Heaven's Door!
How 'bout this…
I'll read your powers,
then inscribe my mandate…
Ow!
What?!
I was given life when Masazo Kinoto
was impaled by the arrow…
I'm Cheap Trap.
But now my user is Rohan Kishibe.
I've relocated to you.
You're my user now.
Wha?!
Understand?
In other words, you're attacking
yourself with a Stand.
You understand, yes?
I'm a Stand with a will of my own.
I may have come into being
through Masazo Kinoto,
but he couldn't control me
as a Stand user.
My whispers inundated his mind,
the terror of being seen
from behind consumed him, yes?
You understand, yes? Understand?
Understand, yes?
My only power is to whisper
nothings into the ears of my host.
Yes? You understand,
so let's burn those pictures.
Dirty leech, get off me!
Dammit, you bastard…
I have to get you off me!
It's simple.
You just have to show me off.
Just show someone your back…
Yes? I'll leave you and
take hold of another soul.
Just a quick flash is all it takes.
Afternoon, Rohan-sensei!
I'm an avid reader.
Now, don't forget the nudes, 'kay…
That's nude women, 'kay!
See, ya!
Let's incinerate those photos, yes?
JULY 15TH (THURS) 12:47 PM
Josuke!
The bullet didn't get him.
Y-You asshole!
Shining Diamond, eh?
Well, I guess the rumors
were right,
taking a bullet point blank
poses no problem…
Freaky, right?
Bite it, Josuke Higashikata.
Chomp down on that lip.
Will he bite?!
Bite it! Come on,
show me that bite,
show me your mark of fear!
So this is his Stand?
What a pathetic, third rate Stand,
just like that old man
in the photo!
Still won't bite, eh…
Trying to cover up
your fear with anger, eh…
I suppose I must.
I guess it's time
for the big reveal.
Smug bastard… You're dead!
Something's off.. this is too weird.
He's been hiding
this whole time,
why would he come out now?
This is all a trap.
He made himself appear now
so that you would attack him!
This guy's dangerous…
Get the hell outta there, Josuke!
It's true… I guess I've got
a pathetic, third rate Stand.
But I suppose
if I had to explain it…
It would be that I can transform
almost anything
into a piece of paper to be filed
discretely and conveniently.
In fact,
this here is Koichi Hirose.
You bastard… So that's
where you were hiding Koichi!
I'm picking up Koichi's scent.
He wasn't holding on to one of
Koichi's belongings… He had Koichi!
Of course, he's alive…
My Stand is pathetic
and third rate, after all.
It doesn't have the power or
ability to kill someone.
But if someone were to
tear it into little pieces,
that's a different story.
I'll let you off easy
and beat you to a bloody pulp,
as long as you bring
Koichi back now.
Try and get him…
If you can.
KOICHI HIROSE
Koichi!
My Stand is pathetic
and third rate, after all.
It doesn't have the power or
ability to kill someone.
But if someone were to
tear it into little pieces,
that's a different story
It's a trap!
I would not go after that paper.
Josuke, ignore it.
There's that bite!
You finally bit it!
Misterioso was waiting for
this moment, Josuke Higashikata!
The moment you bite your lip!
You goddamn, devious, mother…
You just revealed
your mark of fear!
Resist all you like,
your display of anxiety
has made you powerless
before Misterioso.
THUD
I'm really sorry, Josuke,
but I'm glad we made
that little agreement.
If I had tried to help,
he would've gotten me first.
I'm the one with
scent-discerning abilities.
Now do you understand that
Misterioso is the most unstoppable
force the world has ever seen?
W-What?
He's repairing the metal pole…
That's how he's trying to escape.
I'm guessing that piece of paper
is not the one
holding Koichi right now.
I knew that was just a dirty decoy
with "Koichi Hirose" written on it.
You were holding Koichi hostage,
which gave you the confidence
to reveal your true self.
It's because he's alive
that you can threaten me.
I knew that piece of paper
was a trap…
I was pretty damn sure, at least…
But I went after
that little piece of paper
because there was still a chance
it was Koichi.
I don't care if it's a 1 % chance,
that's a chance
I'm just not willing to take!
Misterioso, this is your win.
There's not much more Shining
Diamond can do at this point.
But let me offer you
a little heads-up…
If you do turn me
into a piece of paper,
I'd rip it up into
oblivion real quick.
Cause if I do make it
out of this alive,
I'll freak in knock you dead!
Flattering yourself again I see…
You weren't so tough.
KOICHI HIROSE
Yuya Fungami, huh?
Not helping out Josuke
was a very wise move.
I could have easily
disposed of you.
Your mark of fear
is a stroke of the chin.
But the old man in the photo
never told me to kill you,
so I guess you escaped death.
Smart move, my friend.
Wanna hear something interesting?
This paper…
Anyone can release its contents
by the simple act of unfolding.
Straightforward, yes,
but for someone consumed with fear,
it's surprisingly difficult.
Morioh Grand Hotel, please.
Superb! Koichi Hirose
and Josuke Higashikata
have been disposed of!
Now, Rohan Kishibe
should be enjoying the same…
JULY 15TH (THURS) 2:21 PM
Which one?
Which one has something to do
with Yoshikage Kira?
Which picture is that old man
so worried about?
Burn them, okay? Just burn.
It's no use…
They're just aren't enough clues.
So let's burn the pictures, yes?
Shut up!
You're getting on my nerves!
Damn it! I have to let them know…
I have to let somebody know
TERUNOSUKE MIYAMOTO
JULY 15TH (THURS) 1:20 PM
Er, that was
Morioh Grand Hotel, right?
That's right.
Spending the night?
Well, I've got a lot
to take care of…
A lot, indeed…
No…
I can't let you go to
Morioh Grand Hotel.
Josuke, you bastard! Pompous ass…
If one of them were turned into
a piece of paper, if…
I can't believe I'm saying this…
If anything like that ever happened
to my loving, supporting girls…
If it happened to any one of them,
You bastard, I'd do the exact same!
Besides, how'd that make me look
if I let you or Yoshikage Kira
live in this town.
Hand over Koichi!
This, however, is not a wise move.
So you're saying
you want to take me on?
Which means you're saying you want
to make an enemy of Kira's father?
So be it!
63, 64, 65 kilometers…
It may not be a powerhouse,
but Highway Go Go
is a relentless hunter.
The taxi stopped…
But we're not at the hotel.
No one's getting out of the taxi.
I'm picking up his scent
loud and clear from the car…
But where is he?
Where is he hiding?
The scent of this paper…
There's no question…
This paper smells like
Koichi and Josuke!
Wait, Highway Go Go!
Don't open the door yet.
Bastard, he thinks I'm an idiot.
He's planted another trap.
Trying to lure me in, huh?
Fine, I accept your challenge!
I said I'd fight you!
He wants me to be afraid.
The question is,
how's he gonna do it?
I've gotta find out.
What the? What's this piece
of paper stuck in the door?
Underestimating me again.
This scent…
This piece of paper is a trap.
And I figured out what kind, too.
Open the door, Highway Go Go.
FOOM
So he can turn fire
into paper, too…
I see through your little trick!
Josuke, Koichi,
I'll get both of you out of there!
But I'm picking up
Josuke, Koichi, and something else…
I'm going to have to be
very careful…
What's going on?
I've never smelled this before,
and it's moving around.
It's faint,
and it's moving around inside…
What?!
Crap! Highway Go Go!
W-What is this stuff?
Some kind of chemical?
Shit, it's one thing after another…
W-Wait…
I'm smelling iron now.
Okay, just calm down.
Remember, he wants me to be scared.
If I freak out, he wins.
Iron…
What is it? A machine?
Damn it!
I just hafta open it!
KOICHI HIROSE
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
Josuke! Koichi!
Electricity…
He can hide electricity in paper!
That mechanical smell is…
KOICHI HIROSE
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
A…
A shredder!
It won't turn off!
It's pulling Josuke and Koichi in!
Damn it! Highway Go Go!
I-It's no use.
Highway Go Go isn't strong enough
to stop this thing!
Josuke! Koichi!
You finally did it, Yuya Fungami.
The onset of fear,
followed by a touch to the chin…
Fear is so not a good look on you.
Scaring you was
surprisingly simple, Yuya Fungami!
Misterioso can turn absolutely
anyone into a piece of paper!
Anyone, any time!
Anytime? That's why it's so great!
It instantly transforms its target
into a piece of paper…
Isn't that great!
Fine, you win.
You really got me there.
To tell you the truth,
I couldn't be happier to lose.
Being a flimsy piece of paper
has its advantages,
How else could I reach inside
the shredder!
What did you just pull out?!
You better not unfold
that piece of paper!
I'll turn into a piece
of paper any day.
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
KOICHI HIROSE
Yuya Fungami… I guess you…
kinda, sorta are a cool guy.
Josuke Higashikata… Koichi Hirose…
S-Stay back, Josuke!
Get a load of this!
I-I'll rip it to pieces!
Yuya Fungami
is in this piece of paper!
Act 3! 3 Freeze!
The pressure…
Now, what was it?
I know there's something
I'm forgetting here…
Oh, that's right.
I think I said I'd kill you.
Yeah, I definitely said that.
I think I also said I'd never
forgive someone like you.
Someone who takes hostages…
Someone who uses
psychological blackmail…
W-Wait a minute!
I just wanted to observe
people's reaction to fear stimuli!
I just acquired my Stand,
so I guess I got
a little carried away.
I'm sorry. I feel horrible now.
You know, there's something
I noticed about you…
Huh?
I think you squint one eye
when you're scared.
I guess you could say it's a habit.
But…
When you really freak out
you close both.
You like observing people, huh?
Then go right ahead.
But you're gonna keep
your mouth shut and behave.
I-I'm a book…
The young Misterioso,
Terunosuke Miyamoto,
human book and out of commission.
Josuke never bothered reading it,
but instead donated it
to the Morioh Library
Just mention "Misterioso"
to any librarian,
and you can read it in house.
Borrowing is forbidden.
Don't be surprised,
you may hear a faint voice.
Well, that's taken care of.
MORIOH LIBRARY
Why do I feel like
I've spoken too soon…
But this means we're that much
closer to catching Yoshikage Kira.
But we still got no clues.
Dammit all…
resilient little bastards!
JULY 15TH (THURS) 4:10 PM
Calling them for help won't work.
Get cracking and ignite
those photos, yes?
JULY 15TH (THURS) 4:30 PM
All right,
I'm heading out for a bit.
Where are you going?
To find our leads
as soon as possible,
I'll investigate where
each missing person was last seen.
A person, no matter
how hard he or she tries,
can never escape
their innate personality.
There's no question,
he will make his move.
JULY 15TH (THURS) 4:52 PM
I'll catch him…
I'll find my proof
that Dad isn't Dad
I promise I will.
EPISODE 34
JULY 15TH (THURS), PART 4